始まりも無いと　ぼやいて歩くだけ
This way home has no origin
そんな帰り道
and I walk it feeling just morosely.
君の声が聞こえ
When I heard your voice
振り返られずに　胸を痛めてた
I didn’t need to turn around for my chest to hurt.
誰もいない空　期待してたり…
I expect something from the forsaken sky...
何も出来ないと諦めて
But I give up since I can’t do anything
同じ帰り道　そんな毎日
While I lament about the same way home
ヤダよヤダよとか嘆いたら
And the same routine I’m sick of
雫、無数の音
Droplets, the sound of innumerable of them.
雨宿り、二人きり
Together we take shelter from the rain
目線も合わせずに　言葉を探してる
Searching for words without any eye contact
やまないで夕立　永遠に隠してよ
Don’t stop, evening shower! Hide us forever.
二人の隠れ処を　優しく包んでよ
Gently enwrap our hiding spot.
そんなこともあって
Even if this happens
また好きになって　そして近づけず…
I fall in love again without getting any closer…
意識しすぎなんだ　でもきっかけとか　あれば…
I may be too cautious, but if there is a chance…
苦労しない
I should not worry.
誰もいない空　また君が来て
The sky is forsaken and you come again.
待って！準備とかいるんです
Wait! I do have prepared
だけどまたポツリ　空が怪しい
But it drizzles and the sky looks ominous.
運命いたずら　困ります！
Fate tricked me - it will turn my plans upside down!
雫、無数の音
Droplets, the sound of innumerable of them.
雨宿り、二人きり
Together we take shelter from the rain.
目線がたまに会い　言葉が紡がれる
Sometimes our gazes meet, connected by words.
やまないで夕立 永遠に隠してよ
Don’t stop, evening shower! Hide us forever.
二人の隠れ処を優しく包んでよ
Gently enwrap our hiding spot.
照れた顔がいいの？
Is your embarrassed face any good?
君はズルい人ね
You sure are cunning!
二人だけの空　期待してたり
I expect something from our sky…
途切れ途切れでも嬉しくて
It’s erratic but I’m happy
同じ帰り道　そんな毎日
Because I always dreamed
ずっとずっと夢見てたから
About the same way home and the same routine.
雫、無限の恋　泣いてるよ、
Droplets, the sound of infinite love.
雨の中
It’s crying in the rain
二人の行方など　誰も知らないけど
Though no one knows about our whereabouts.
やまないで夕立　永遠に隠してよ
Don’t stop, evening shower! Hide us forever.
傘が二人の距離　縮めてくれるから
The umbrella is the reason the distance between us shortens after all.
ちょっとだけ照れた顔　自信になってるよ
Your slightly embarrassed face becomes my confidence.